You just tell me when刚才你告诉我时，
you're rolling.你滚动。
We're rolling.我们正在滚动。
A lot of people--很多人 -
have questioned有质疑
what really happened.究竟发生了什么事。
And when the novel并且当新的
was first published,第一次出版，
it didn't take long没多久
for there to be even有甚至
more questions asked.问更多的问题。
It's always它总是
remained a mystery.仍然是一个谜。
And that's why这就是为什么
I wanted to thank you我要感谢你
for coming为未来
in to meet with us.在与我们见面。
To help shed some为了帮助了解一些
light on the events.亮起的事件。
Okay.好吧。
He dedicated他专门
the book to you.本书给你。
Can you tell us你能告诉我们
how much of his novel他的小说有多少
was based on fact?以事实为依据？
All of it.所有这一切。
It was 1969--那是1969年 -
What can you tell us你能告诉我们
about that summer?那年夏天呢？
Question?问题吗？ What was是什么
the question?这个问题吗？
What do you remember about that你还记得什么
summer 1969?夏天的1969年？
It was hot.它是热的。
It was real hot.这是真正的热。
God must have been sweatin',上帝一定是出汗的，
it was so hot.它是如此热。
Tell me about the murder.告诉我的谋杀案。
Hey, how much, how much I'm gettin'嘿，多少钱，我是多么得“
paid for this?为此付出了吗？
Well, Sheriff Call好吧，警长呼叫
was this evil, nasty,这邪恶的，肮脏，
26 26
disgusting son恶心的儿子
of a gun.一炮。
27 27
Black people黑人
hated Sheriff Call恨警长呼叫
28 28
because he killed因为他杀死
so many of us所以我们很多人
29 29
during his two terms在他的两个任期
in service.服务。
30 30
Some of my family我的家人
was included.被列入。
31 31
White people白为民
feared him too.担心他。
32 32
So somebody got fed up因此，有人厌倦了
with his fat ass, and killed him.他的屁股，将他打死。
33 33
That's what happened这是发生了什么事
that summer.那个夏天。
34 34
They say he dragged他们说，他拖着
his intestines他的肠子
35 35
for a mile一英里
before he died.在他去世前。
36 36
Crazy white people even疯狂的白色人甚至
built a statue for him.为他建一座雕像。
37 37
How did it come about怎么会约
38 38
that you worked你的工作
for the Jansens?为的Jansens吗？
39 39
I was cleaning我被清洗
for them part time,他们的一部分时间，
40 40
right when his mamma右，当他的妈妈
ran off.跑了。
41 41
And Ward and I,沃德和我，
Ward was his brother,沃德是他的兄弟，
42 42
he was in high school他在高中
at the time在时间
43 43
and we raised而我们提出
him together.他在一起了。
44 44
Little Jackie小成龙
was five at the time.是在时间5。
45 45
Where was his father?他的父亲在哪里？
46 46
W. W. was just W. W.只是
47 47
chasing girls,追女孩，
you know.你知道的。
48 48
And running而运行
the local newspaper.当地的报纸。
49 49
The Moat County Tribune.护城河县论坛。
50 50
How's Ward?病房吗？
51 51
He's good, he's good.他的好，他的好。
Real busy.真正的忙。
52 52
Ward was a writer--沃德是一位作家 -
53 53
uh--for the Miami Times.呃 - 在迈阿密的时代。
54 54
He used to write他用写
about, uh-- ，呃 -
55 55
well, he was kind of famous,不错，他是著名的一种，
you know,你知道吗，
56 56
'cause he wrote about the Civil因为他写了关于公务员
Rights Movement民权运动
57 57
and the poor穷人
and the unjustly accused.和不公正的指责。
58 58
That's how come这是怎么来的
that lady Charlotte那女的夏洛特
59 59
started writing开始写
letters to him.他的信。
60 60
Stuff like that.类似的东西。
61 61
Yeah.是啊。
62 62
And then Jack, like I said,然后，杰克，就像我说的，
he was a swimmer.他是一个游泳健将。
63 63
And, uh--还有，嗯 -
64 64
almost professional,几乎专业，
very close but then非常接近，但
65 65
he got kicked他被踢
off the swim team,关闭游泳队，
66 66
he got kicked他被踢
out of college,走出大学校门，
67 67
and he came back home to his papa's和他回家的时候他爸爸的
house to deliver newspapers.房子，送报纸。
68 68
He didn't want他不希望
to come back home,回家，
69 69
but he didn't have但他并没有
nowhere else to go.无处可去。
70 70
# Yeah # ＃呀＃
71 71
# Mmm # ＃嗯＃
72 72
Jack, you better turn杰克，你的好
that music down.音乐声关小。
73 73
You know W. W.你知道W. W.
gon' be mad at you.坤'在你疯了。
74 74
Dang it, Anita, can you当它，梅艳芳，您可以
please knock?请敲？
75 75
I could've been我可以一直
jerking off in here.在这里抽风了。
76 76
Please, it ain't nothing拜托，也不是什么
I ain't seen before.以前我也没见过。
77 77
What are you doing?你在做什么？
78 78
I'm picking up your stuff,我拿起你的东西，
like I do every day.像我这样的每一天。
79 79
Oh come on, not today.哦，拜托，不是今天。
It's too hot for that.这是太热了。
80 80
I'm just helping.我只是帮助。
81 81
You're not helping me.你不帮我。
You don't have to help me.你一定要帮我。
82 82
Come on.来吧。
83 83
Get off the bed下车的床
so I can make it.所以，我也能做到。
84 84
Go fix me去解决我
some collard greens.一些羽衣甘蓝。
85 85
It's my bed.这是我的床。
86 86
I know it's your bed.我知道这是你的床。
Really?真的吗？
87 87
Because it's your bed,因为这是你的床，
you should fucking make it.你应该他妈的做到这一点。
88 88
They cancelled他们取消
"The Smothers Brothers." “窒息兄弟。”
89 89
Oh, no, that's your show.哦，不，那是你的节目。
90 90
Well, I love that show.嗯，我喜欢这个节目。
I love Dick and I love Tommy.我爱我和迪克爱汤米。
91 91
Lay down.躺了下来。 Let me be you for a second.让我成为你的第二个。
Oh, yeah, right.哦，是的，没错。 Get me in trouble.让我麻烦了。
92 92
You want to be me,你想成为我，
I get to be you?我得到是你吗？ Okay.好吧。
93 93
Okay, I'll love this.好吧，我喜欢这一点。
Jack, may I come in?杰克，我可以进来吗？
94 94
Oh, good, okay.哦，好，没问题。 Go away, go out.走开，走出去。
Go back out.回去了。
95 95
Okay.好吧。 I better start jerking我要开始抽搐
off first.先关闭。 Okay.好吧。
96 96
Jack, sorry to interrupt杰克，对不起打断
your masturbation,您的手淫，
97 97
but I'm here但我在这里
to clean the bed!清洗床上了！
98 98
I could've been jerking off.我一直在抽搐。
I'm gonna clean everything!我要干净的一切！
99 99
I could have我可以有
been jerking off!被抽风了！
100 100
Get out!滚出去！
Clean my shit up!清洁我的屎！
101 101
...get all that we ...让所有的
have received in return,已收到的回报，
102 102
is just another只不过是另一种
smooth exercise顺利行权
103 103
in political manipulation.在政治操作。
Good girl.好女孩。
104 104
Deceit and deception,欺骗，欺骗，
105 105
callousness and indifference无情和冷漠
to our individual problems,我们每一个人的问题，
106 106
and the disgusting playing恶心的播放
of divisive politics,分裂的政治，
107 107
pitting the young点蚀的年轻人
against the old,不服老，
108 108
labor against management,劳动对管理，
north against south.北方对南方。
109 109
Did you want你有没有想
to see me?见我吗？
110 110
Have you spoken你说话
to Ward this week? Ward的这个星期？
111 111
No.号
Hello, Jack.你好，杰克。
112 112
He didn't mention anything to you他没有提到任何你
about coming here?来这儿吗？
113 113
I can't believe your father's making我真不敢相信你父亲的决策
me report on this.我报告。
114 114
I mean, look at her.我的意思是，看看她的。
115 115
... ... to open our society.打开我们的社会。
116 116
She plans to run她计划运行
for president next.总统的未来。
117 117
They want to talk他们想谈谈
to Hillary Van Wetter.到希拉里·范多雨。
118 118
Don't you let that Pulitzer不要再让普利策奖
Prize fool you.奖欺骗你。
119 119
He don't know他不知道
everything yet.一切还。
120 120
Ain't no reason是不是没有原因
to come up here来这里
121 121
stirring up shit搅拌狗屎
with that asshole.那个混蛋。
122 122
I just wanted to say我只想说，
that it is very important这是非常重要的
123 123
for all Americans为所有的美国人
to recognize--认识到 -
124 124
Charlotte Bless loved夏洛特保佑爱
her some dangerous men.她的一些危险的人。
125 125
She wrote men in prison.她写道：在监狱里的人。
126 126
She finally fell她终于倒下了
in love with one.爱一个。
127 127
She was determined她决心
to get him out.让他出来。
128 128
Why y'all ain't got为什么你们都没有得到
no ice in here?在这里没有冰？
129 129
You want ice,你要冰，
go to your house.去你家。
130 130
Charlotte.夏洛特。
131 131
Oh, that's my show.哦，那是我的节目。
What you think, Charlotte?你认为，夏洛特？
132 132
I don't like it.我不喜欢它。
Make it looser.它更宽松。
133 133
That's that nigger这就是那个黑鬼
you've been writing?你在写什么？
134 134
No. This is号，这是
my white man.我的白人。
135 135
Ohhh.哦〜〜。
136 136
What happened yesterday?昨天发生了什么事？
I missed it.我错过了。
137 137
Listen to this.听着这一点。 He thinks I'm他认为我
his angel.他的天使。
138 138
His angel?他的天使吗？ Shhh.嘘。
Shut your face.闭上你的脸。
139 139
Bitch, how old is he?母狗，他几岁了？
Oh, my God.哦，我的上帝。
140 140
He's a fine motherfucker that's trying to他是一个的细狗娘养的，是试图
fuck you.你他妈的。 "Ever there was an angel in the world, “曾经有一个天使在人间，
141 141
"my angel, it must be you, “我的天使，一定是你，
142 142
but no angel would do the things但没有天使会做的事情，
I dream that you want."我的梦想，你想要的。“
143 143
Your angel, his angel.你的天使，他的天使。
144 144
Mm-hm.嗯。
That's hot.这是热的。
145 145
He say, "If you truly exist,他说，“如果你真的存在，
I may become a religious man."我可能会成为一个虔诚的人。“
146 146
Ah! “啊！
147 147
"All my life, my heart has tried “我的生活，我的心一直试图
to find a place找一个地方
148 148
I cannot name...a home."我不能说出一个家。“
149 149
You need to find你需要找到
yourself a young one.自己年轻的一个。
150 150
He'll fuck you他会他妈的你
real good.真正的好。
151 151
He says他说，
I'm his home.我是他的家。 Hm.嗯。
152 152
Got a hundred我百
different men不同的男人
153 153
writing her写她的
from the penitentiary.从监狱。
154 154
That's her man.这是她的男人。
155 155
Oh, no.哦，不。
This is my man.这是我的男人。
156 156
This here's the one.我们在这里可以看到，这是一个。
157 157
Mm-hm.嗯。
158 158
Ward came home沃德回家了
to investigate调查
159 159
the conviction的信念
of Hillary Van Wetter.希拉里·范·多雨。
160 160
The town wasn't镇是不
too happy about it太高兴
161 161
and neither was his papa.也不是他的爸爸。
Oh, shit.哦，该死。 Ugh.唉。
162 162
Ward--沃德 -
163 163
there's a horse有一个马
in the parking lot.在停车场。
164 164
It's our ride这是我们乘坐
home, Yardley.家庭，亿利。
165 165
Uh, where is everybody?呃，是每个人都在哪里呢？
166 166
It's Sunday.这是星期天。
167 167
People's either at home人民无论是在家里
or at church.或在教堂。
168 168
It's a shithole.这是一个shithole。
169 169
Hey, man.嘿，伙计。
170 170
Hey, you.嘿，你。
171 171
How you doing?你怎么样？
172 172
Jack, meet杰克，满足
Yardley Acheman.亿利Acheman。 Hey.嘿。
173 173
My little brother, Jack.我的小兄弟，杰克。
The swimmer, right?游泳者，对不对？
174 174
Yeah, he's our driver now.是啊，他现在是我们的驱动程序。
Right, good.是的，不错的。
175 175
Here, let me get these.在这里，让我得到这些。
176 176
That's my typewriter.这是我的打字机。
You've gotten big, boy.你已经得到了大，小男孩。
177 177
Just be careful只是要小心
with the typewriter.打字机。
178 178
Got all pumped up.得到了所有抽了。
Is that from swimming?那是从游泳吗？
179 179
Not anymore.现在不一样了。
180 180
No! “不！” No! “不！” No! “不！”
181 181
Yardley's real particular亿利真正特别的
about his suits关于他的西装
182 182
and his typewriter.他的打字机。
Well, it's very expensive.嗯，这是非常昂贵的。
183 183
Yes.是。 Thank you.谢谢。
184 184
How do I get in?我如何获得？
185 185
Watch your head.小心你的头。
186 186
Don't touch my head.不要碰我的头。 Tell him告诉他，
where you're from, Yardley.你来自哪里，亿利。
187 187
London.伦敦。
188 188
Ah! “啊！
189 189
When I came here--当我来到这里 -
from New York,从纽约，
190 190
I was interviewing我在采访
for the job--的工作 -
191 191
and I was in advertising我是在广告
in New York在纽约
192 192
and I mentioned that it was simply和我提到，这是根本
different in New York.不同在纽约。
193 193
So how'd you get那么你是怎么得到
from New York City从纽约市
194 194
to the metropolis大都市
of Lately, Florida?最近，佛罗里达州？
195 195
Jansen residence.詹森居住。
196 196
So I came down South and于是，我来到了南亚和
I interviewed at the paper.我采访的文件。
197 197
W.W., Miss Roberta's W.W.，​​Roberta的小姐
on the phone.在手机上。
198 198
No, no, no.不，不，不。
199 199
We don't take我们不
phone calls.电话。 Anita...梅艳芳...
200 200
Who's Miss Roberta?谁是小姐罗伯塔？
No calls, Anita.没有电话，梅艳芳。
201 201
What part of London什么样的伦敦
you from, Yardley?你亿利？
202 202
Um, all over London.嗯，遍布伦敦。
203 203
Is there a good dry cleaning here?是否有一个良好的干洗吗？
Excuse me?请原谅我吗？
204 204
Dry cleaning.干洗。
205 205
Dry cleaning?干洗吗？
Yes.是。
206 206
You ain't gonna eat你是不是会吃
that, are you? ，是吧？ Uh-uh.嗯，嗯。
207 207
How you gonna win those swimming你怎么会赢得那些游泳
meets if you don't eat?满足，如果你不吃吗？
208 208
I'm retired.我退休了。
209 209
Retired.退休了。 Jack, you ain't even tired杰克，你甚至不累
enough to be retired.足够的退休。
210 210
How is it exactly它到底是怎样
you guys work?你们的工作吗？
211 211
I mean, like that boy我的意思是，喜欢那个男孩
drowned at his initiation?淹死在他萌生了吗？
212 212
Well, Yardley's the writer--那么，亿利的作家 -
213 213
And I'd guess you'd say我猜你会说
Ward is the nuts and bolts.沃德是螺母和螺栓。
214 214
Yeah.是啊。 When I was当我
a reporter,记者，
215 215
we had rewrite men who took我们不得不重写男人谁了
the stories over the phone.在电话里的故事。
216 216
No, no, no.不，不，不。
I'm not a rewrite man.我不是一个重写的人。
217 217
I'm the writer.我是作家。
218 218
I'm the one who puts我是一个谁把
the facts into perspective.事实的角度。
219 219
Oh!哦！
220 220
Yes.是。 It's a different这是一个不同的
world now, Mr. Jansen.现在世界上，詹森先生。
221 221
Clearly.很明显。
222 222
Times have changed此一时
a bit, sir.了一下，先生。
223 223
What interest does感兴趣的是什么
"The Miami Times" “迈阿密时报”
224 224
have in Hillary在希拉里
Van Wetter?凡多雨？
225 225
He murdered他谋杀
somebody in jail?在监狱里的人吗？
226 226
Even if he was guilty--即使他是有罪的 -
227 227
It was a lynching, pure and simple.私刑，这是一个纯粹而简单。
--he had certain rights. - 他有一定的权利。
228 228
And even乃至
if he was guilty--如果他是有罪的 -
229 229
Hillary has rights that the process希拉里权利的过程
completely disregarded.完全忽略不计。
230 230
And that's why这就是为什么
we're here.我们在这里。
231 231
I'm very sorry, everybody,我很抱歉，大家好，
but I'm going to have to leave.但我将不得不离开。
232 232
I'm sorry, sweetheart.对不起，亲爱的。
233 233
I have early evaluations我有早期评估
first thing in the morning.在早上的第一件事。
234 234
Come here, sugar.来到这里，糖。
I apologize.我向你道歉。
235 235
All right, buddy.好吧，伙计。
236 236
Ward?病房？
237 237
Good night, boys.晚上，男孩。
238 238
Ward?病房？
239 239
Seems mighty sure似乎是强大的肯定
of himself for a colored.自己的彩色。
240 240
Ward said沃德说：
they need a driver.他们所需要的驱动程序。
241 241
A driver?驱动程序？
242 242
What you do out there?你做什么了吗？
243 243
So you meet anybody new所以你遇到的任何新的
out there in Miami?赫然出现在迈阿密吗？
244 244
I met a few.我遇到了几个。
245 245
Oh, yeah.哦，是的。 All types down there,所有类型出现了下滑，
you know?你知道吗？
246 246
You stay away你远离
from those rough ones.从这些粗糙的。
247 247
Remember what happened还记得发生了什么事
the last time.最后一次了。
248 248
How your kids?你的孩子呢？
249 249
You look beautiful, babe.你看起来很漂亮，宝贝。
250 250
They're doing good.他们正在做的不错。
They're doing really good.他们做的非常好。
251 251
As soon as I get当我得到
out of here,离开这里，
252 252
I'll go see them and make dinner我去看看他们，使晚餐
all over again.从头再来。
253 253
You should come你一定要来
to that dinner, too.晚餐，太。
254 254
I'll come我会回来
to that dinner.该晚宴。
255 255
I think Ellen is我认为艾伦是
maybe number four--也许四 -
256 256
since you left.自从你离开。
257 257
Yeah.是啊。
258 258
That's why I don't take这就是为什么我不
them bitches too seriously.他们母狗太认真。
259 259
They come and they go他们来和他们去
and they come and they go.他们的到来，和他们去。
260 260
You know你知道吗
what I mean?我的意思是什么？
261 261
# At last ＃在最后
My dreams come true #我的梦想成真＃
262 262
# Today he said "I do" # ＃今天，他说：“我做”＃
263 263
# Friends said ＃朋友说，
It couldn't be done #它不能做到＃
264 264
# But all his love ＃但是他的爱
I know I've won #我知道我已经赢得了＃
265 265
How you doing there, Yard?你在那里做什么，院子吗？
Oh, jeez.噢，天啊。
266 266
# That's where he placed ＃这是他放置的地方
The wedding band #结婚戒指＃
267 267
Hey, close嘿，关闭
that door, boy.那扇门，男孩。
268 268
I don't want your daddy我不希望你的爸爸
screaming about all the flies所有的苍蝇尖叫
269 269
getting in the house.得到的房子。
270 270
Hmm.嗯。
271 271
Who is that, Jack?那是谁，杰克？
272 272
Uh--呃 -
273 273
I'm looking for the office我在寻找办公室
of Mr. Jansen.詹森先生。
274 274
Ward Jansen沃德詹森
of "The Miami Times." “迈阿密时报”。
275 275
I said who is it?我说的是谁呢？
I work for the Times.我工作的时代。
276 276
You do?你怎么办？
Yeah.是啊。
277 277
Huh.呵呵。
278 278
Well, I'm Charlotte Bless.好吧，我是夏洛特保佑。
I'm Jack Jansen.我是杰克强森。
279 279
Here, let me get that.在这里，让我得到这个机会。
Oh.哦。
280 280
Hey.嘿。
All my files.我的所有文件。
281 281
The office该办公室
is in the garage.是在车库里。
282 282
You look a little young你看起来有点年轻
to be a journalist.成为一名记者。
283 283
I'm really just the driver.我真的只是驱动程序。
Oh.哦。
284 284
But I do write.但我写的。
285 285
So do I. I write letters.我也是，我写信。
I'm pretty good.我是相当不错的。
286 286
Hey, guys!嘿，伙计们！
287 287
This here is这里是
Miss Charlotte Bless.夏洛特小姐祝​​福。
288 288
Oh, not for long.哦，时间不长。
289 289
Hillary and I are engaged我和希拉里是从事
to be married.要结婚了。
290 290
Hello, Miss Bless.你好，小姐祝福。
I'm Ward.我的病房。
291 291
Oh, Mr. Ward, good to finally哦，Ward先生，好到最后
meet you.见到你。
292 292
You didn't mention the engagement你没有提到的参与
in your letters.您的来信。 Go clean yourself up.去清理自己。
293 293
Well, it only just happened.好了，它只是发生了。
He just proposed.他只是建议。
294 294
Oh, that looks nasty.哦，那长得坏坏的。
Well, how did I do that?好了，我怎么做呢？
295 295
Excuse me a second.对不起，我第二次。
296 296
Get Miss Bless something to drink.获取小姐保佑喝的东西。
I'm Yardley Acheman.我是：亿利Acheman。
297 297
We thought you我们想你
and Hillary hadn't met.和希拉里还没有得到满足。
298 298
Well, only in pictures,那么，只有在图片，
299 299
but we been writing但我们一直在写
each other for months几个月彼此
300 300
and we understand我们明白
ourselves just perfect.我们只是完美。
301 301
Ward, where should沃德，应该在哪里
I put her files?我把她的档案吗？
302 302
Everything you need to know你需要知道的一切
about Van Wetter有关范多雨的
303 303
that's been in the papers,一直在报纸上，
304 304
is here in these boxes.在这些箱子。
305 305
Our exciting correspondence我们的激动人心的信件
is in that box.是在该框中。
306 306
In case如果
you're interested.你有兴趣。
307 307
My desk, Jackie boy.我的办公桌上，成龙男孩。
308 308
Mr. Jansen, I really just詹森先生，我真的
wanted to thank you.要谢谢你。
309 309
I wanted to thank you我要感谢你
for returning my letters.返回我的信。
310 310
And for helping me get Hillary out对我的帮助得到希拉里
of that hellhole.这个地狱般的地方。
311 311
Well, I wouldn't go好了，我不会去
booking the honeymoon just yet.预订的蜜月，只是还没有。
312 312
But we are going但我们要
to fight his sentence打他的句子
313 313
and the way和方式
it came about.它来的。
314 314
Thank you.谢谢。
Thank you so much.谢谢你这么多。
315 315
Nobody deserves the death penalty,没有人值得死刑，
Miss Bless.小姐祝福。
316 316
Not even甚至没有
Hillary Van Wetter.希拉里·范·多雨。
317 317
Um, excuse me.嗯，对不起。 So, everything is所以，一切是
ordered alphabetically.按字母顺序排列。
318 318
I was telling, um--我说，嗯 -
what's your name?你叫什么名字？
319 319
Yardley.亚德利。
320 320
Um, that all嗯，这一切
of the files,的文件，
321 321
Um, everything that's been嗯，一切的
in the papers,在报纸上，
322 322
is in the top box.在机顶盒。
This is gonna be a great help.这会是一个很大的帮助。
323 323
He's an innocent man.他是一个无辜的人。
You're gonna find that out.你会发现。
324 324
Wrongly convicted.错判。
325 325
This is gonna get us这是会让我们
off to a great start.一个很好的开始。
326 326
I've done a lot of research.我已经做了很多的研究。
I see that.我看到了。
327 327
In the meantime, you need to freshen在此期间，您需要保持充沛的精力
up or anything?或什么？
328 328
Jack, show Miss Bless to the washroom.杰克，表明小姐祝福洗手间。
I think I'll just stay here.我想我会留在这儿。
329 329
You might have some questions你可能有一些问题
that you need answered.你需要回答的。
330 330
I can freshen我可以梳洗
up just here. ，就在这里。
331 331
Cold beer for me, Jack.对我来说，杰克冰镇啤酒。
332 332
You're adorable, Jack.你真可爱，杰克。
333 333
I will take an iced tea我会冰茶
if you have it.如果你拥有了它。
334 334
You want anything, Ward?你想要什么，病房吗？
I'm good.我很好。
335 335
You'll see, uh--你会看到，呃 -
336 336
it's an enormous amount of work--这是一个大量的工作 -
What's with the boxes?是做什么用的箱子？
337 337
I don't know what to do here.我不知道在这里做什么。
What's with the boxes?是做什么用的箱子？
338 338
Well, we're好了，我们是
gonna start on it.我开始就可以了。
339 339
My Jack was in love我的杰克爱
with Charlotte Bless.与夏洛特祝福。
340 340
I could tell我可以告诉
that horny little boy ，角质的小男孩
341 341
wanted to jump her想跳她
on first sight.一见倾心。
342 342
Everybody was confused why she was每个人都在困惑，为什么她
engaged to Hillary Van Wetter.参与到希拉里范多雨。
343 343
Nasty, white trash swamp.讨厌的，白色垃圾沼泽。
344 344
"All the killers “所有的杀手
who have written me谁写我
345 345
want to press their mouths我想按自己的嘴巴
into my vagina进入我的阴道
346 346
and some, even the crack和一些，即使裂纹
of my behind,我的身后，
347 347
except Hillary Van Wetter.除了希拉里·范·多雨。
348 348
He has no such desire.他有没有这样的意愿。
349 349
He wants to be他想
sucked off himself.自己吸走。
350 350
I consider this psychological proof我认为这是心理的证明
of his innocence.他是无辜的。 " “
351 351
She is one nasty她是一个讨厌的
little nut job.小坚果的工作。
352 352
Think we've been taking认为我们已经采取
her a little too seriously.她看得过重。
353 353
You sure get你肯定
bored quick.无聊快。
354 354
No. Can tell I'm not going号可以告诉我不打算
to get laid anytime soon很快得到奠定
355 355
in this Floridian在此佛州
shit pit, so--屎坑，所以 -
356 356
Listen--听着 -
Hey, Kathy, it's me.嘿，凯西，是我。
357 357
Hillary tells her希拉里告诉她
that the knife那把小刀
358 358
Yardley.亚德利。
and the bloodied shirt和血迹斑斑的衬衫
359 359
that the deputies claim代表声称，
to have found in his house在他的房子里发现
360 360
somehow got lost不知何故迷路
before the trial.在审判之前。
361 361
Yeah, I miss you, too.是啊，我很想念你。
362 362
What?什么？
363 363
Hello, Kathy.你好，凯西。
364 364
Miss Bless wanted吴保佑希望
to look at the prison.在监狱里。
365 365
Jack's first assignment杰克的第一项任务
was to take her there.是她。
366 366
I bet he knows我敢打赌，他知道
I'm here.我在这里。
367 367
See, people who fall你看，人谁属于
in love outside--在爱情外 -
368 368
of a normal relationship,一个正常的关系，
369 369
they have these powers--他们拥有这些权力 -
telepathic powers.传心术力量。
370 370
Hillary and I have that kind我和希拉里有那种
of connection, you dig?的连接，你挖？
371 371
Now why ain't you现在为什么不是你
in college?上大学？
372 372
Huh?咦？
373 373
Uh, I was a swimmer when呃，我是游泳运动员
I was in school.我是在学校。
374 374
No kidding?不是开玩笑吧？
Yeah.是啊。
375 375
I was a swimmer.我是一个游泳健将。
You were?你是吗？
376 376
Uh-huh.嗯。 I'd swim我会游泳
like a mermaid像美人鱼
377 377
if it wasn't如果它不是
for my damn curly hair.我该死的卷发。
378 378
I think straight hair我觉得直发
gives me class.让我类。
379 379
All right.好的。
380 380
Good.好。
381 381
So?那又怎样？
382 382
Well, we was drunk one night,好了，我们醉了一晚，
and, uh-- ，呃 -
383 383
I just--我只是 -
384 384
I lost my temper我失去了我的脾气
and just--只是 -
385 385
well, I emptied the pool.好了，我清空池。
386 386
At your college?在你的大学吗？
387 387
The University大学
of Florida.美国佛罗里达州。
388 388
They called that vandalism,他们呼吁，人为破坏，
I guess.我猜。
389 389
It's actually not as easy它实际上不是那么容易
to do as it sounds.这样做，因为它的声音。
390 390
So you lose所以，你失去
your temper often?你的脾气往往吗？
391 391
Mm.嗯。
392 392
This place is full of boys这个地方充满的男孩
just like you跟你一样的
393 393
who lost their temper谁失去了自己的脾气
one day.一天。
394 394
I'm getting horny我越来越角质
being this close to him.正在接近他。
395 395
Oh, baby.哦，宝贝。
396 396
I bet he's horny我敢打赌，他的角质
for me all the time.我所有的时间。
397 397
Yeah.是啊。
398 398
Mmm.嗯。
399 399
Oh, I can feel him.哦，我能感觉到他。
400 400
Can I help you folks?我可以帮你人呢？
401 401
Oh, no.哦，不。
402 402
Yes, Officer.是的，主任。
Uh--hm.嗯 - 嗯。
403 403
We just wanted to sit in your我们只是想坐在你的
parking lot for a little while.停车场一小会儿。
404 404
What for?为什么呢？
405 405
His daddy's in there and we wanted他的爸爸是在那里，我们想
to send him good vibrations.送他良好的振动。
406 406
Some good what?有一些很好的是什么？
407 407
Oh, these special things哦，这些特别的东西
called good vibrations.良好的振动。
408 408
Sorry, ma'am.对不起，夫人。
Y'all can't park here.你们都不能停在这里。
409 409
Oh.哦。
410 410
Yes, Officer.是的，主任。
411 411
The story that Hillary希拉里的故事
told the deputies对人大代表
412 412
was never investigated.从来没有。
413 413
He simply told it once他只说一次
from the witness stand在证人席上
414 414
and was never asked和从来不问
to elaborate,详细说明，
415 415
not even甚至没有
by his own lawyers.由他自己的律师。
416 416
Good to see you again, Ward.很高兴再次见到你，沃德。
Nice to see you.很高兴见到你。
417 417
Sir, this is my writing partner,主席先生，这是我的写作伙伴，
Mr. Yardley Acheman.亿利Acheman先生。
418 418
Of course.当然。
419 419
I suppose我想
the best place to start最好的地方开始
420 420
would be将
the beginning.开始。
421 421
I was born我出生
in this county.在本县。
422 422
1897, to poor 1897年，贫困人口
but proud parents.但自豪的父母。
423 423
Mr. Pine, could we松先生，我们
skip 65 years,跳过65岁，
424 424
save everyone some time?节省大家一些时间呢？
425 425
Hillary Van Wetter, 1965?希拉里·范·多雨，1965年？
426 426
Oh, I can't agree to talk to you哦，我不能同意你说话
about that matter.那件事。
427 427
Not without不无
my client's permission.我的客户端的权限。
428 428
He's entitled to his privacy,他有权以自己的隐私，
just like anybody else.就像其他任何人。
429 429
You have his permission.你有他的许可。
He wrote you.他写信给你。
430 430
I'll have to check我不得不检查
that out.说了出来。
431 431
I'm sure the letters would be我敢肯定的信，
in your files, Mr. Pine.在你的文件中，松先生。
432 432
That's what you say,这是你说的话，
but I have a client to protect.但我有一个客户端保护。
433 433
Look here.看这里。
434 434
If we have to get a lawyer of如果我们要得到一个律师
our own down here我们自己在这里
435 435
to sort this out,排序了这一点，
then while he's here,然后，当他在这里，
436 436
we're gonna have him look through every我们要他看起来每
aspect of Mr. Van Wetter's case.方面，凡先生多雨的情况下。
437 437
Including the competency包括能力
of his defense.他的辩护。
438 438
There was nothing wrong with the defense有什么不对的防御
Hillary Van Wetter got in court!范多雨希拉里在法庭上了！
439 439
Then you have nothing然后你有什么
to worry about from us.从我们担心。
440 440
We just want我们只是希望
to talk to him.和他谈谈。
441 441
Then we'll be然后，我们将
out of your--从你的 -
442 442
You don't know a thing你不知道的事
about this person!关于这个人！
443 443
You've been in this world你已经在这个世界上
for five minutes, boy!五分钟后，孩子！
444 444
Now that's just现在，这只是
not necessary, Mr. Pine.没有必要的，松先生。
445 445
Yes.是。 I talk the way I want我想，我说话的方式
in my office!在我的办公室！
446 446
All right.好的。 Then you'll arrange然后，你会安排
the meeting, will you?会上，你愿意吗？
447 447
Quick!快！
We're gonna be late!我们要迟到了！
448 448
You get你得到的
the marriage license?领结婚证吗？
449 449
I can't believe我简直不敢相信
we're doing this!我们这样做！
450 450
Fuck!他妈的！ Jack, go knock杰克，敲
on the door again.在门上。
451 451
There she is.在那里，她是。
Whoa, baby哇，宝贝
452 452
Well, I say-- Good morning,好吧，我说 - 早上好，
Miss Bless.小姐祝福。
453 453
Look at Daisy Mae.看看菊花的美。
454 454
Morning.早上好。
455 455
You look你看
just fine.就好了。
456 456
Hope he likes it.希望他喜欢。
457 457
Uh--呃 -
458 458
Would you mind putting你介意把
up the windows?上窗户吗？
459 459
It's gonna muss my hair.它会弄脏我的头发。
460 460
Are you serious?你是认真的吗？
461 461
I'm sweating like a pregnant nun我出汗像一个怀孕的尼姑
back here.回到这里。
462 462
Unbelievable!太不可思议了！
463 463
Hi.你好。
464 464
You got 15 minutes.你得到15分。
465 465
No physical contact没有身体接触
of any kind.任何一种。
466 466
No tape recorders.没有录音机。
467 467
No object may be passed可以传递任何对象
to the prisoner.的囚犯。
468 468
I'll be right我马上就
outside this door.外门。
469 469
Mr. Van Wetter,凡先生多雨，
470 470
my name is Ward J ansen.我的名字是沃德ĴANSEN。
471 471
This is my associate, Yardley Acheman--这我的联营公司，亿利Acheman  -
You look like your picture.你看起来像你的照片。
472 472
Mmm.嗯。
I do?怎么办？
473 473
Thank you.谢谢。
474 474
These your这些是你的
paperboys?报童？
475 475
Mm-hm.嗯。
476 476
What they gonna do他们怎么办
for us?我们呢？
477 477
They gonna save you.他们会救你。
478 478
They're gonna save us?他们会救我们吗？
479 479
Mm-hm.嗯。
480 480
Shit.妈的。 They can't even他们甚至不能
save themselves.自救。
481 481
Mr. Van Wetter,凡先生多雨，
we wanted to ask you我们想问问你
482 482
about the lost evidence有关的证据丢失
in your case.你的情况。
483 483
Shut up.闭嘴。 Can't you see难道你不明白
I'm busy?我正忙着吗？
484 484
Will you do something你会做什么
for me right now?对我来说现在好了吗？
485 485
Oh.哦。
Oh, I wish I could.哦，我希望我可以。
486 486
Spread your legs open你的腿伸展开
a little bit.一点点。
487 487
Mmm.嗯。
Yeah.是啊。
488 488
Now tear off现在撕下
them pantyhose.他们的裤袜。
489 489
Rip those off. RIP那些关闭。
490 490
Yeah.是啊。
Mm-hm.嗯。
491 491
Move your hands away.移动你的手离开。
Mmm.嗯。
492 492
Yeah.是啊。
493 493
Now open现在打开
up your mouth--你的嘴 -
494 494
you picture what you wrote你想象你写的文章
me in your letters.我在您的来信。
495 495
You bitch!你这婊子！
496 496
Oh, I love you.哦，我爱你。
497 497
What the hell's什么是地狱的
going on in here?在这里吗？
498 498
You're a good girl.你是个好女孩。 I warned y'all!我警告你们都！
This visit's over!这次访问结束！
499 499
I told y'all this visit was--我告诉你们都为这次访问 -
come on!加油！
500 500
Come on, Hillary.来吧，希拉里。
No! “不！”
501 501
There's nothing going on!没有什么！
502 502
Shit!妈的！
No! “不！”
503 503
What the fuck?怎么回事？
I didn't touch that girl!我没碰那个女孩！
504 504
No! “不！”
505 505
What the fuck什么他妈的
you laughing about?你在笑什么？
506 506
Come on now,来吧，
Miss Bless.小姐祝福。
507 507
Jack came home杰克回家了
and threw up after that.后扔了。
508 508
He couldn't believe他简直不敢相信
he still loved her他仍然爱她
509 509
after what he saw,之后，他所看到的，
but he did.但他做到了。
510 510
You're Ward Ward's boy?你的受监护人的孩子吗？
Mm-hm.嗯。
511 511
Most contrary man最相反的人
in all of Moat County.在护城河县。
512 512
What may I do for you我可以为你做什么
gentlemen today?君子呢？
513 513
It's about the murder它的谋杀案
of Sheriff Call.的谢里夫电话。
514 514
I understand that there's据我所知，有
some physical evidence一些物证
515 515
relating to the case有关的情况下的
that was lost?我们失去了什么？
516 516
Yes, sir.是的，先生。
I believe there was.我相信有。
517 517
Well, we was wondering好了，我们想知道
what sort of explanation什么样的解释
518 518
the department might have.部门可能有。
519 519
I wish I knew.我希望我知道。
520 520
Mr. Van Wetter once cut凡先生多雨剪过一次
a deputy's thumb off.一个副拇指。
521 521
Did you know that?你知道吗？
522 522
It was over a traffic ticket,一切都结束了一张罚单，
if I remember.如果我没有记错。
523 523
You can't do much你不能做太多
without your thumb.没有你的拇指。
524 524
It's what separates us这是我们
from the primates.从灵长类动物。
525 525
For a little thing like holding对于一个小东西，如控股
your wife's titty.你妻子的奶操。
526 526
You're not married,你还没结婚，
Mr. Jansen?先生詹森？ No.号
527 527
A little thing like that,这样的一件小事，
you can't do it.你不能做到这一点。
528 528
Maybe I'll just go talk也许我会去谈话
to the deputies代表们
529 529
who was involved谁是参与
in the arrest.在执行逮捕。
530 530
You can talk您能谈谈
to whoever you want你想给谁
531 531
as long as they'll talk to you.只要他们就会跟你说话。
But they won't.但他们不会。
532 532
And why is that?这是为什么？
533 533
They haven't forgotten他们没有忘记
what Hillary did to one of theirs.希拉里对他们的。
534 534
The judge法官
allowed testimony允许证词
535 535
based on evidence根据证据
that he never even saw.他甚至从来没有看到。
536 536
He took the officer's word他把官员的话
over Hillary's.对希拉里的。
537 537
I can't say I blame him.我不能说我怪他。
Nobody does.没有人做。
538 538
You got me你让我
in the face there.在那里面对。
539 539
So you've got所以，你有
to ask him.问他。
540 540
Where was he
between 2:00 and 6:00?
541 541
I'm gonna ask him
about some things he wrote,
542 542
some letters to Charlotte.
543 543
H ere we go.
544 544
Hold.
545 545
Good morning,早上好！
Mr. Van Wetter.
546 546
Hey.嘿。
547 547
Where's your dress?
548 548
You don't like me
like this?这样的吗？
549 549
You know a prisoner
by the name of--
550 550
Ward, Ward, Ward.
551 551
You know a prisoner
by the name
552 552
of Mr. Bobby Valentine?
Mr. Van Wetter?
553 553
Mr. Demarcus Williams,
Mr. Bobby Hinton?
554 554
Another prisoner另一名犯人
by the name of Jimmy Edwards,
555 555
another one, Demarcus.
556 556
I think his name is Curt.
I forgot his last name.
557 557
Anyway, you know what
they all have in common?
558 558
Hey, Martin Luther King.
559 559
You know what they all had
in common?共通之处？ What?什么？
560 560
They all wear pants.
561 561
Every goddamned man
in here wears pants!
562 562
How am I supposed to tell
you apart from them?
563 563
Don't talk to her like that!
Sit down, Jack.
564 564
Sit the fuck down.坐的我坐下。
565 565
Mr. Van Wetter, we don't have
a lot of time, all right?
566 566
We got to move on.
567 567
You're gonna move
on one way or another, Ward?
568 568
Ward's in charge!
569 569
He's gonna get his way--
till he don't.
570 570
Maybe that's how he got
his scars on the face.
571 571
You mentioned in one
of your letters to Miss Bless
572 572
that you was working
Turn around, bitch!
573 573
An Uncle Tyree--
Yeah, yeah.是啊，是啊。
574 574
at the time在时间
of the murder.
575 575
What kind of work you doing?
Lawn work.
576 576
577 577
You wear a dress
in here next time
578 578
or you don't bother coming!
Bitch, look at me!
579 579
And stop bringing
that fucking nigger
580 580
think he
Muhammad Ali with you!
581 581
Mr. Van Wetter,
come have a seat.
582 582
Cassius Clay, nigger.
583 583
We can get a dress
here in five minutes.
584 584
Why don't you你为什么不
have a seat?
585 585
Go home, boy!
586 586
I don't know--我不知道 -
587 587
Charlotte, where does one get
pants like that from anyway?
588 588
Well, I think we got
the case licked.
589 589
This is这是
a fucking circus!
590 590
In this town,
591 591
Weldon Pine helped get
Sheriff Call re-elected.
592 592
Tension was brewing
in the house.在房子里。
593 593
Jack was getting jealous of
Hillary and Charlotte.
594 594
And he was getting jealous
of Ward and Yardley, too.
595 595
Ward wasn't somebody who
attached himself to just anybody.
596 596
Your dad's girlfriend,
what's her name?她叫什么名字？
597 597
Jack couldn't understand why he
was so attached to that Yardley.
598 598
No, you didn't.
599 599
What is the hottest
temperature温度
600 600
that you've ever been in?
601 601
125. 125。
602 602
How about you?你怎么样？
603 603
Just put your hand out
and it burns off
604 604
The hottest was when I lived
in Florida. How about you?你怎么样？
605 605
It doesn't bother me.它不打扰我。
I never pay attention to it.
606 606
Cold and wet just goes
fucking through you like a knife
607 607
but--I don't know.
608 608
So how's Mr. Van Wetter today?
He still innocent?
609 609
I don't know.我不知道。
If he is--
610 610
he sure as hell didn't have no help
proving it,
611 611
not from that
Weldon Pine guy anyway.
612 612
Could I have a fork
or something?还是什么？
613 613
The chicken legs, you eat those
with your hands.
614 614
Maybe at your house.
615 615
This is这是
the South, sugar.
616 616
Anyway, you know
how I feel about that.
617 617
Do you eat your mashed potatoes with
your hands? Do you really want to--?
618 618
Do you really want to--?
Bring me some chopsticks, Anita.
619 619
Do you really want
to take the shot--
620 620
on putting to death
a man or a woman一个男人或一个女人
621 621
when maybe they're innocent?
I mean, I don't.
622 622
I don't want to try to have
to live with that.
623 623
On the other hand-- Are you gonna
eat that or torture it?
624 624
Told you,
I'm not hungry.
625 625
That's'cause
you're in love.
626 626
I know who you're
sniffing around, too.
627 627
Anita, please don't tease him
at the table.在餐桌上。
628 628
On the other hand,另一方面，
if somebody's guilty,
629 629
well, you want to pay
their room and board 365?
630 630
Absolutely.当然可以。
Ah! “啊！
631 631
Whoops.哎呀。
632 632
I'm so sorry.我很抱歉。
633 633
Anyway, it's just iced tea.
It ain't even gonna stain.
634 634
You'da thought Jack woulda
had a girlfriend by now,
635 635
but all he did was jerk
off to the pictures
636 636
in those nudie magazines
that was under his bed.
637 637
Now she was all he could think
of night and day.
638 638
Oh, yeah, he was
definitely in love.
639 639
He needed her.他需要她。
640 640
What you reading?
You give it to me.
641 641
What is this shit?
" Lolita."
642 642
Porno, I bet.
643 643
Oh.哦。
644 644
You need a girlfriend.
645 645
Look at them girls
over there.那边。
646 646
Go on and introduce yourself.
Go on.去吧。
647 647
I'm just fine我就好了
right here.
648 648
You want me to blow you,
don't you?不是吗？
649 649
You don't have to answer.你没有回答。
I know it's true.
650 650
I'm not gonna blow
a friendship--
651 651
over a stupid
little blowjob.
652 652
You hear me?
653 653
Look, why you talking
to me like that?
654 654
See that one in blue?
She'll blow you.
655 655
I don't want someone like
that blowing me.
656 656
It's a good thing
you're not in prison
657 657
because you wouldn't have
a choice there.
658 658
Fuck you.你他妈的。
659 659
Jack, come back here.
660 660
# Well, well #
661 661
# I passed the corner
Where we first met #
662 662
# Yes, I did #
663 663
# Memories of our love
Linger there yet #
664 664
# Oh, I'm sitting
On top of the world #
665 665
# Just to know
That you're my girl #
666 666
# I'm just lucky #
667 667
# I'm lucky, lucky,
Lucky in love #
668 668
# Our love is here--#
669 669
# Lucky, lucky, lucky
In love--#
670 670
# Oh, I'm sitting
On top of the world #
671 671
# Just to know
That she's my girl #
672 672
# That makes me lucky #
673 673
Oh my God.哦，我的上帝。
Pam.帕姆。
674 674
# I'm so lucky lucky
Lucky in love #
675 675
# Let me sing
One more time ##
676 676
What is that?那是什么？
Is he okay?他还好吗？
677 677
Is he having
an allergic reaction?
678 678
A jellyfish sting
or something?还是什么？
679 679
A fucking jellyfish
did that.这样做。
680 680
You're supposed to piss
on a jellyfish sting.
681 681
We're gonna have to do
something embarrassing.
682 682
You got to hang
in there.在那里。 Hey!嘿！
683 683
Well, you're gonna--
You'll piss on him?
684 684
What are you你是什​​么
doing to him?
685 685
Call an ambulance.
686 686
He's having a reaction!
Shut the fuck up!闭嘴！
687 687
Don't push me!
You're supposed to piss--
688 688
Get the fuck out of here!获取他妈的离开这里！
I can see this.
689 689
I can see he's poisoned.
You don't pee on--
690 690
Don't push me!
I will slap your face.
691 691
Get the fuck out of here.获取他妈的离开这里。
All right.好的。
692 692
I said, I will kick your ass!
I'm going to call the police.我要叫警察。
693 693
Move it!动起来！
Fine.精细。
694 694
If anyone's gonna piss
on him, it's gonna be me!
695 695
Fine, fuck you!
696 696
He don't like strangers
peeing on him!
697 697
Come on.来吧。 Come on.来吧。
698 698
Come on, baby come on!
Wake up!醒醒吧！
699 699
Come on!来吧！ Shit!妈的！
700 700
# La la la #
701 701
# Zippeydoo da #
702 702
Come on.来吧。
703 703
Come on!来吧！
704 704
# No matter
What people say #
705 705
# I know our love
Is here to stay #
706 706
# And I'm so lucky #
707 707
You're gonna be okay!
708 708
# Lucky lucky in love #
709 709
# I'm mister lucky #
710 710
# I'm so lucky
Lucky lucky in love ##
711 711
Jack.杰克。
712 712
What are you doing here?你在这里做什么？
713 713
What do you think你怎么看
I'm doing here?
714 714
Told you to knock
on my door
715 715
before you come
in my room.在我的房间里。
716 716
Oh, hush up.
717 717
Here, I brought
you something.
718 718
Take these pills.
719 719
I smell awful.
720 720
That's because that blond
lady peed all over your face.
721 721
Ugh.唉。 Here,在这里，
drink this.
722 722
Does it hurt?会不会痛？
723 723
I'm cold, I'm cold,
I'm cold.
724 724
Congratulations, Jack.
We're in the paper.
725 725
"Fast action saves
Lately man at beach.
726 726
"Miss Charlotte Bless
of Mobile, Alabama
727 727
apparently saved
Mr. Jansen's life
728 728
by urinating over the areas
of his body
729 729
where he was attacked.
730 730
These included the victim's arms,
genitals and face. " “
731 731
Jack, I had no idea.
732 732
I had no idea我不知道
that your own father
733 733
would print
something like that.类似的东西。
734 734
It made the AP wire.
735 735
You're famous
all over the country.全国各地。
736 736
"Home Remedy."
Good title.
737 737
What's Dad trying
to do to me?
738 738
It's called the newspaper
business, Jack.
739 739
Oh, shit.哦，该死。
740 740
Let him go, Jack!
You're gonna kill him.
741 741
Jack, let him go.
742 742
You put your hands
on me again,
743 743
I will fuck you up!
Yeah?是吗？
744 744
Fuck you, nigger!
745 745
He needs to get laid.
746 746
He needs
a fucking straitjacket.
747 747
He's sexually repressed.
748 748
Sexually repressed
is a 40-year-old woman
749 749
who's obsessed
with prison cock!
750 750
That's not nice.这不是很好。
Calm down now.
751 751
No, fuck calm down!
752 752
I'm not having
some kid call me a nigger.
753 753
I want him我想他
out of here now!
754 754
Yardley?
755 755
Jack, let's go杰克，让我们去
to the prison.
756 756
You two can stay here
and keep arguing.
757 757
This time I'm talking
to Hillary by myself.
758 758
Come on.来吧。
759 759
He's not even
gonna look at you
760 760
if I'm not there
in a pretty dress.
761 761
Well, that's too bad
for him.他。
762 762
Ward.
763 763
You'll see.你会看到的。
764 764
I knew Jack
didn't mean to say it.
765 765
But those were the times
we were living in
766 766
and it was
what it was.
767 767
Yardley, on the other
hand, well--
768 768
# Get out of the cold #
769 769
# Take the night off #
770 770
# Be your own boss #
771 771
# When you're near me #
772 772
# Can you hear me #
773 773
# Or do I have to shout
In your ear #
774 774
# Mmm #
775 775
# Take the night off #
776 776
# Turn the light on #
777 777
# Take the night off #
778 778
# Turn the light on #
779 779
Forensic report says
that the sheriff
780 780
was stabbed
between 2 and 3 AM.
781 781
Yep.是的。 Like I told you,
782 782
I was with-- my Uncle Tyree
doing lawn work
783 783
in Ormond Beach
at the time.的时间。
784 784
Lawn work?
Yes, sir.是的，先生。
785 785
You mean stealing?
Yes, sir.是的，先生。
786 786
Stealing sod
off a golf course.
787 787
A developer paid through
the teeth for that shit.
788 788
We sold it and we didn't
make it back
789 789
to the river
till sunrise.
790 790
What kind of developers?
Condominiums, man.
791 791
You got a name?你有名字吗？
No, I don't.不，我不知道。
792 792
Deputies say they found
the sheriff's body at 6 AM--
793 793
but it was the way
he was killed.
794 794
That's what makes everybody
assume it was you.
795 795
What you think?你觉得呢？
You tell me.你告诉我。
796 796
I ain't the only one carrying
a machete around here.
797 797
True.为True。
798 798
The deputies
went to Tyree's house,
799 799
he said he'd been sleeping
in bed all night
800 800
and had a whole bunch of family
members there to confirm it.
801 801
Then they go
to your house--
802 802
where they find the bloodstained shirt
and knife.
803 803
Yeah, all right.
Listen to me.听我说。
804 804
Every knife and shirt that
I own is stained in blood.
805 805
It's what I do这是我做什么
for a living.
806 806
I'm gutting alligators
for their skin.
807 807
Okay?可以吗？
I was a bachelor.
808 808
I didn't have nobody
to do my laundry.
809 809
You probably got somebody
to do your laundry.
810 810
What you think?你觉得呢？
811 811
I bet you do.我敢打赌，你怎么做。
812 812
They never matched the blood
to the sheriff's, did they?
813 813
Tell me how to find Tyree.
814 814
The arms of mercy
are so wide
815 815
they will accept any man,
816 816
but they will not accept
any man wearing pants.
817 817
Where is my woman?
818 818
Where's my woman?
819 819
The only one you need只有一个你需要的
to talk to right now is me, baby.
820 820
The only one
I need to talk to?
821 821
I'm the only one.
I'm your mercy.
822 822
I'm your arms wide open,
I'm your pants.
823 823
Ward's in charge!
824 824
If you wanna go see Tyree,
I'll give you directions,
825 825
but you got to make that choice
because he's a violent man.
826 826
Now stay with me now
827 827
because this is
when it gets tricky.
828 828
Ward called Charlotte
829 829
and told her to drive Yardley
to Ormond Beach.
830 830
He wanted to verify Hillary's
so-called golf course story.
831 831
The boys went on to visit
this Uncle Tyree.
832 832
Man, this is stupid.
Where are we going?我们要去哪里？
833 833
No one lives out here.
No one could live out here.
834 834
You talk to Anita about your--choice
of words?
835 835
It was fucked up.它搞砸了。
836 836
I know.我知道。
837 837
Goddamn it.该死的。
838 838
Sure you don't me
to watch the car?
839 839
Goddamn it! This stuff
ain't working, man.
840 840
It's like they
like this shit.
841 841
Better than jellyfish,
I bet.我敢打赌。
842 842
Fuck!他妈的！
Oh, my God!哦，我的上帝！
843 843
Watch it!当心！ You're way too
close to him. Ward! Ward!
844 844
You better jump him.
845 845
It's better in here
where we have to get lower.
846 846
Ward, you're sinking!
847 847
This whole place
is just floating.
848 848
You ever think
about Mama?
849 849
I wonder我不知道
where she at.
850 850
She is in Tucson, Arizona.
851 851
You got a girlfriend?
852 852
Why?为什么呢？
853 853
You don't remember this, but
Mom used to go on about, uh--
854 854
don't make love to a woman until
you get married, right? Mm-hm.嗯。
855 855
I followed that
until I was--
856 856
Oh, fuck that. We'll talk我们将讨论
about it later.
857 857
Let's go.让我们去。
858 858
Mr. Van Wetter?
859 859
Good afternoon, sir.
860 860
My name is Ward Jansen.
I work for "The Miami Times. "
861 861
We're here on behalf here
of your nephew, Hillary.
862 862
You lost a shoe.
863 863
You're lucky it was
just the one.
864 864
Snakes all around here.
865 865
We need to talk to you about your nephew,
Mr. Van Wetter.
866 866
Little late for that,
isn't it?不是吗？
867 867
He gonna be strapped
to a chair and electrocuted.
868 868
Well--
869 869
you come all the way up here
just to tell me that?
870 870
You could've saved
yourself a trip.
871 871
He tells me
that he was with you
872 872
the night Sheriff Call
was murdered,
873 873
stealing sod,
which you later sold.
874 874
Let's hope
nobody believes him.
875 875
Stealing's against the law,
ain't it?
876 876
Now he's still got time.
877 877
I don't much care
for you.给你。
878 878
Come up here
in my home--
879 879
and call me a thief.
880 880
I ain't up here about thieving,
Mr. Van Wetter.
881 881
I'm up here about whether a man's life
needs to be taken or not--
882 882
for the murder
of Sheriff Call.
883 883
But if you was with your nephew
that night,
884 884
it's vital for Hillary
that you admit it.
885 885
I don't think我不认为
he likes you much.
886 886
I don't like him
much either.
887 887
Where's the ice cream?
888 888
It's coming.它的到来。
889 889
Keep that baby quiet.
890 890
What's wrong这是怎么回事
with that baby?
891 891
All right, well, sit on it.
892 892
Yeah.是啊。
893 893
You want--?
894 894
You want a little ice cream?
895 895
You don't want
to have any ice cream.
896 896
You take this chair
out here with me.
897 897
No sense you staying
over there.那边。
898 898
Thank you.谢谢。
899 899
Little man, get yourself
a chair there.
900 900
Get yourself a chair.
901 901
Was you with him?
902 902
Yeah.是啊。
903 903
Well, I--
904 904
I was with him.
905 905
Where?在哪里？
906 906
Golf club.
907 907
Ormond Beach.
908 908
Stole sod, sold it--
909 909
to this one到这一个
condo developer.
910 910
Where's Hillary
live from here?
911 911
We didn't get back
till the morning, sunrise.
912 912
He lives that way.
913 913
So why are you那么，为什么你
telling me now?
914 914
You seem like the only person
thinks Hillary's innocent.
915 915
No, sir, Mr. Van Wetter.
No, sir.不，先生。
916 916
I didn't say that.我没有这样说。
917 917
Your boy--
918 918
he's getting
nervous over there.
919 919
Let's go.让我们去。 I'm done我所做的一切
talking to you.
920 920
What you hiding?
Ward?
921 921
I'm sick--
922 922
of your questions.您的问题。
923 923
Eugene?
924 924
Ward, remember the first day
when I was with Charlotte? Yeah?是吗？
925 925
We went and stopped
at the prison.
926 926
We didn't go in.
I saw him.我看见了他。
927 927
Tyree?
Yeah.是啊。
928 928
What you think?你觉得呢？ They was getting
their stories together?
929 929
I don't know.我不知道。
930 930
I'll tell you this.
931 931
They ain't as dumb
as they look.
932 932
Oh, shit, man.
933 933
Fuck.他妈的。
934 934
What the fuck, man?你他妈的，男人吗？
935 935
Leave me
at the fucking hotel?
936 936
Jesus!天哪！
937 937
In Yardley's room,
no less.
938 938
Fuck, man.
Look at you.看看你。
939 939
You're becoming obsessed
with this case.
940 940
Wake me up.我叫醒。
941 941
942 942
Come on.来吧。
943 943
You look terrible, Ward.
944 944
Those mosquitoes eat
you for breakfast?
945 945
Yardley found
the golf course.高尔夫球场。
946 946
You found the golf course?
What's he doing in my clothes?
947 947
The car broke down.
948 948
we had to walk
into town,
949 949
stopped by the motel
to freshen up.
950 950
Get out of my clothes now.
951 951
Come on.来吧。
952 952
Come on, Jack.
953 953
What are you doing?你在做什么？
954 954
Miss Bless.
Come on, stop it.
955 955
Jack!杰克！
956 956
On the morning
of the murder
957 957
the grounds superintendent
of the Ormond Beach Golf Course
958 958
phoned the
Police Department警察局
959 959
to report that four
of his greens
960 960
had been stripped
in the night.在夜间。
961 961
You talked to the
superintendent? No.号
962 962
He died, but I found
another guy who remembered
963 963
that the club
called the governor
964 964
to ask him to declare them
a disaster area
965 965
so they could get
federal funds
966 966
to replace the greens.
967 967
It gets better.它变得更好。
968 968
I found the builder, too,
969 969
the guy who bought
the stolen greens.
970 970
He remembered
Hillary and Tyree.
971 971
They showed up
at 6 AM in a truck.
972 972
He took one look at them
and what they had
973 973
and thought they'd stolen
it from a cemetery.
974 974
But of course, he doesn't want to
be connected to this in any way.
975 975
And who was he?
976 976
Well, the only way
he'd talk to me
977 977
is if I promised
to keep him anonymous.
978 978
Come on now.
What's his name?他叫什么名字？
979 979
No, no, no.不，不，不。
980 980
I've got to keep it anonymous.
I gave him my word.
981 981
He's got, well,
he's in a position
982 982
to get some work from the state,
so you know.
983 983
But good, huh?
984 984
Outstanding.杰出。
985 985
How'd you find him?
986 986
Building permits.
987 987
Damn building permit.
988 988
Time to get out of Lately.
989 989
Did you sleep
with Yardley?
990 990
You know, people
like Yardley, you just--
991 991
got to get him
on your side.
992 992
You know what I mean?你明白我的意思吗？
993 993
You fucked him for that?
994 994
Fucking a man is the most natural
thing in the world, Jack.
995 995
It is.是的。
996 996
997 997
I kind of like it我倒是很喜欢它
out here.
998 998
This was这是
a good idea.
999 999
Oooh!哦！
1000 1000
Come on!来吧！
Let's dance.
1001 1001
Come on!来吧！
No! “不！”
1002 1002
Come on, Jack.
Got to have fun!
1003 1003
You wanna dance?你想跳舞吗？
1004 1004
Yeah!是啊！ I wanna dance
with you!与您合作！
1005 1005
Woo!呜！ You're good!你是优秀的！
1006 1006
This is not me这不是我
apologizing, you dig?
1007 1007
I just don't like我只是不喜欢
to see you sad.
1008 1008
Yardley told their editor
about the new evidence
1009 1009
from Ormond Beach.
1010 1010
This was enough to show injustice
in the legal system of Lately
1011 1011
and enough for a good story.
1012 1012
Yardley wanted to get
out of town
1013 1013
and Ward knew it.
1014 1014
All these peanuts
on the floor.在地板上。
1015 1015
Pigs.猪。 Bunch of pigs
living around here.
1016 1016
Sick of this shit.
1017 1017
I can't find我无法找到
Mama's ring.
1018 1018
Oh, well, a nigger
must have come
1019 1019
in the middle of the night半夜
and stole it.
1020 1020
I'm sorry, Anita.
1021 1021
I didn't mean to say--
1022 1022
I didn't mean我不是故意的
to say that.
1023 1023
And I'm really sorry.
1024 1024
You know, Jackie, you got to watch
your mouth.你的嘴。
1025 1025
Somebody'll cut your little ass
over some shit like that.
1026 1026
You understand me, boy?
1027 1027
Yes, ma'am.是的，夫人。
1028 1028
And you miss
your mother?你妈妈呢？
1029 1029
Sometimes.
1030 1030
It's a dis-damn grace
the way she left you.
1031 1031
And I been here.
1032 1032
Well, let's find
this ring, I guess.
1033 2052
No, that's all right.
I can find it.
1034 1034
Ohhh.
Sorry.抱歉。
1035 1035
All right.好的。
1036 1036
Okay.好吧。
1037 1037
I'm really sorry.我真的很抱歉。
Okay.好吧。
1038 1038
All right, Jack.
1039 1039
What's makes
this story any different?
1040 1040
What makes your story different
than the others, John?
1041 1041
What makes this case so different that you
want to pull the plug now?
1042 1042
The facts.
What's left to do?剩下要做的是什么？
1043 1043
You've been up there
a month and a half.
1044 1044
I want我想
your ass back here.
1045 1045
Save that shit
for someone else.
1046 1046
I'm not comfortable with it
and you shouldn't be either.
1047 1047
I'm going to Ormond Beach
to get the facts.
1048 1048
I want to get some
alligator shoes.
1049 1049
You run this article,
this shit could hurt me.
1050 1050
I got advertisers
to think of.
1051 1051
A dvertisers? You want你想
me to be concerned
1052 1052
with the advertisers
for your newspaper?
1053 1053
Ward, you don't
know everything.
1054 1054
He knows
what he's doing, Pa.
1055 1055
Shut up!闭嘴！ I'm not我不
talking to you.
1056 1056
He knows
how to get stories,
1057 1057
but what he doesn't
fully appreciate
1058 1058
is that the stories
go out into a community.
1059 1059
They resonate.
1060 1060
Oh, like the jellyfish?
1061 1061
Like getting pissed on?
1062 1062
You notice Anita's been acting
mighty bossy recently?
1063 1063
She's always been
that way.这种方式。 Yeah.是啊。
1064 1064
Oh, shit.哦，该死。
1065 1065
Darling, let it go.
Don't get yourself hurt.
1066 1066
Sit down.坐下。
I'll get Anita. Anita!梅艳芳！
1067 1067
Hey, I'll take
care of it.呵护它。
1068 1068
Anita will get it. Anita!梅艳芳！ Does she难道她
have children? I can't remember.我不记得了。
1069 1069
She got two kids.
Oh, yeah.哦，是的。
1070 1070
How you doing, baby doll?
Where you going?你要去哪里？
1071 1071
Hoo.
A baby shower.
1072 1072
Um, Anita, uh,
before you go,
1073 1073
could you clean
up this mess.
1074 1074
I said I got it. It's all right.它的所有权利。
Anita's got it.
1075 1075
I got it.我得到了它。
1076 1076
1077 1077
We're going我们将
to Ormond Beach.
1078 1078
Oh, just come right
out and tell them.
1079 1079
I've named Ellen
editor-in-chief.
1080 1080
And--
1081 1081
we're getting married.我们就要结婚了。
1082 1082
It's an antique.
1083 1083
I know it is.
1084 1084
This belonged
to my mother.
1085 1085
It was a gift from me.
Give it back, Jack.
1086 1086
Just give it
back to her.
1087 1087
It's all I got.
1088 1088
Ward never believed
Yardley's story.
1089 1089
Building permits
and anonymous sources.
1090 1090
He took Charlotte and Jack
back to Ormond Beach
1091 1091
to get to the bottom of it.
1092 1092
Yardley went back home
to Miami.迈阿密。
1093 1093
# That man is dangerous #
1094 1094
# Loving him is dangerous #
1095 1095
# That man is dangerous #
1096 1096
# Loving him is dangerous #
1097 1097
# That man is dangerous #
1098 1098
What is that builder's name,
Charlotte?夏洛特？
1099 1099
What builder?
1100 1100
You know你知道吗
exactly what builder.
1101 1101
The one Yardley
says bought the sod.
1102 1102
I don't know.我不知道。
He went alone.
1103 1103
I went我去了
to the hairdresser's.
1104 1104
Takes a lot
to look like this.
1105 1105
Charlotte Bless,
you is a mess.
1106 1106
And you'd do anything
to get your man
1107 1107
out of jail--
wouldn't you?不是吗？
1108 1108
Thirsty, huh?
1109 1109
Oh, yeah.哦，是的。
1110 1110
# That man is dangerous #
1111 1111
You keep staring
like that,
1112 1112
we're gonna have
a problem.一个问题。
1113 1113
What really happened到底发生了什么
down there, Charlotte?
1114 1114
After you went to the hairdresser,
what happened?发生了什么？ Hm?嗯？
1115 1115
Jack, would you tell your brother to get
his hands off of me?
1116 1116
Come on, man.来吧，伙计。 Let's go somewhere else.
Easy, little brother.
1117 1117
Just fucking relax, boy.
1118 1118
Miss Bless ain't got
no answer, huh?
1119 1119
I didn't think so.我不这么认为。
1120 1120
Your brother's
acting strange.
1121 1121
Not used to drinking
like this.是这样的。
1122 1122
# Is this love affair for real
Or is it just one and done? # ＃
1123 1123
# I'm telling you #
1124 1124
A little more多一点
than that.比。
1125 1125
Why is Ward doing this?
1126 1126
We got 50 places
to be tomorrow.
1127 1127
What is that?那是什么？
1128 1128
It's beautiful.它的美丽。
1129 1129
Don't turn it down.
1130 1130
No one's ever given me
something like this before.
1131 1131
Well, you just tell me
when you want it back, huh?
1132 1132
It's beautiful.它的美丽。
1133 1133
You want me你要我
to fuck you, Jack?
1134 1134
Then I'm gonna fuck you
any way you want.任何你想要的方式。
1135 1135
Jack.杰克。
1136 1136
Jack!杰克！
1137 1137
I want to get我想要得到的
some alligator shoes.
1138 1138
Mmm, Jack.
1139 1139
You wanted您想
your ass whupped.
1140 1140
Is that what you wanted?这是你想要的吗？
1141 1141
Tell me请告诉我
what you want.你想要什么。
1142 1142
You're a dirty pig.
1143 1143
I'll fuck you我会他妈的你
any way you want.任何你想要的方式。
1144 1144
Little white pig.
1145 1145
Jack?杰克？ Jack!杰克！ Jack!杰克！
1146 1146
Jack, wake up!
1147 1147
Something's going
on in Ward's room.
1148 1148
Hey!嘿！ Hey!嘿！
1149 1149
Stop it!住手！
1150 1150
What the fuck?怎么回事？
1151 1151
Help!请帮助我！
We need help!我们需要帮助！
1152 1152
Where's the fucking keys?
1153 1153
Where's the fucking keys,
you piece of shit?
1154 1154
Motherfucker, wake up!
1155 1155
Help!请帮助我！
1156 1156
Where are在哪里
the fucking keys?
1157 1157
Ward, what's
the plastic for?
1158 1158
What is the plastic?
1159 1159
What the fuck?怎么回事？
1160 1160
I've watched you so often.
1161 1161
You sit here, and I heard
that you play a little drum.
1162 1162
You didn't get up
and do anything. No.号
1163 1163
I heard you could sing,
1164 1164
but with me you
are going to sing.
1165 1165
He's gonna be fine.
1166 1166
You don't have to sleep
all the way down there.
1167 1167
All right.好的。
1168 1168
Just this once.
1169 1169
I can't fuck
with this TV on.
1170 1170
Feels kind of awkward
to be talking
1171 1171
while you see this.
1172 1172
But it's kind of awkward that
they're doing it in the first place.
1173 1173
Most boys Jack's age
fall in love坠入爱河
1174 1174
with their high school
or college sweetheart,
1175 1175
but Jack never bothered
much with girls
1176 1176
after his mama left.
1177 1177
I guess you could say
he had abandonment issues.
1178 1178
With Charlotte, it was like he
was getting his mama,
1179 1179
his high school sweetheart,
and a oversexed Barbie doll
1180 1180
all rolled into one.
1181 1181
Anywho, I think
y'all seen enough.
1182 1182
My hair looks like crap.
Don't even look at it.
1183 1183
Oh, shit.哦，该死。
1184 1184
I got to go
to the hairdresser.
1185 1185
My wig
ain't acting right.
1186 1186
I don't understand我不明白
what the fuck什么他妈的
1187 1187
you're doing
with Hillary.
1188 1188
Oh.哦。
1189 1189
Here we go.在这里，我们走了。
1190 1190
You don't love him.
1191 1191
Really?真的吗？
Mm-hm.嗯。
1192 1192
You don't know that.你不知道。
1193 1193
You don't know anything.你什么都不知道。
1194 1194
You're 20 years old.
You're not that much older.
1195 1195
I'm a lot older.
1196 1196
It ain't gonna happen.
1197 1197
Look at me.
1198 1198
It's not practical.
1199 1199
I'm not as practical
as the murderer?
1200 1200
He's not guilty, Jack.
That's the point.这是一点。
1201 1201
That's not the point.这不是问题的关键。
Fuck this.他妈的这个。 I knew it would happen.
1202 1202
What?什么？
1203 1203
I give you some ass
and suddenly--
1204 1204
Look--Hillary
ain't so bad.
1205 1205
And I'm not so good.
1206 1206
I've got another side.
1207 1207
I got a fucked-up side,
1208 1208
and it gets along
just fine with my man.
1209 1209
You can't split
yourself into sides.
1210 1210
Sure, you can.
Just ask your brother.
1211 1211
What the fuck does Ward
have to do with this?
1212 1212
He has a dark side and I don't mean
him being a fag.
1213 1213
Now these boys
lived for each other.
1214 1214
Jack wasn't hurt by Ward
being a homosexual
1215 1215
or the dark stuff
that he was into.
1216 1216
He was just hurt
that Ward never told him.
1217 1217
Hi.你好。
Hey, there.嘿，你好。
1218 1218
H e's doing better.
He's gonna be all right. Good.好。
1219 1219
So, I gotta go.
1220 1220
Go where?去哪里？
Where you going?你要去哪里？
1221 1221
I'm going back home.
1222 1222
You don't have
to go anywhere.
1223 1223
It's just the way这只是方式
it works.它的工作原理。
1224 1224
You shouldn't go anywhere
you don't want to go.
1225 1225
Who says谁说：
I don't want to go?
1226 1226
Why do you have to go?
1227 1227
'Cause I do.
1228 1228
Take this ring back.
1229 1229
Yardley called the hotel.
1230 1230
Did you tell him?
1231 1231
I told him Ward got mugged
and beaten on the beach.
1232 1232
Well, what'd he say?
1233 1233
Not much.没有多少。
1234 1234
Wanted to know
if he was gonna make it.
1235 1235
When I told him
it wasn't serious,
1236 1236
he kind of just lost interest.
He's not gonna be much help for a while.
1237 1237
Didn't sound like he needed
much help.
1238 1238
He can't go write the story
alone, Charlotte.
1239 1239
Well, we'll just have to see.
He doesn't know enough about it.
1240 1240
This isn't about
a newspaper article, Jack.
1241 1241
It's about
a person's life.
1242 1242
That's the whole point
we're here, okay?
1243 1243
So it's about
someone's life.
1244 1244
Baby, don't go.
1245 1245
You're starting to screw
with my head.
1246 1246
Look, you're a good kid,
all right?没事吧？
1247 1247
You're--
1248 1248
You got your whole life
ahead of you,
1249 1249
and you want me?
1250 1250
Jack went down
to "The Miami Times"
1251 1251
to try to stop Yardley
from publishing the article.
1252 1252
He didn't want
his brother's name on it.
1253 1253
Jack.杰克。
1254 1254
Hi.你好。
1255 1255
Hey.嘿。 How's Ward?
How's your brother doing?
1256 1256
Been trying to get ahold
of you since yesterday.
1257 1257
Good.好。 He's obviously
not doing so badly then.
1258 1258
Sorry, I didn't want
any distractions. Come, sit, sit.
1259 1259
He wants to read
what you're writing.
1260 1260
A s soon as I'm done, he'll be the first
to read it, as always.
1261 1261
Damn it!该死！ I'm so sick
of your shit, man!
1262 1262
His name他的名字
is on that, too.
1263 1263
He wants to read it
before it's published.
1264 1264
Okay?可以吗？ That's it.就是这样。
Uh-huh.嗯。
1265 1265
He just wants to read it
before it's published.
1266 1266
You got to get
those facts straight.
1267 1267
You got to get
all the facts straight.
1268 1268
You're starting to sound
like your brother.
1269 1269
Look, we have
a deadline here.
1270 1270
I've told you, this is
the newspaper business.
1271 1271
We don't have time
to get all the facts.
1272 1272
We both know the town
of Lately set Hillary up.
1273 1273
We've got the story.
It's not the fucking truth!
1274 1274
You want to talk
about the motherfucking truth?
1275 1275
You thought
I was from London?
1276 1276
Ain't no Negro getting
a job up in this spot
1277 1277
unless he's a colored
motherfucking James Bond, you dig?
1278 1278
I got drunk once
and let Ward suck my dick.
1279 1279
He got a taste for niggers
and now he hates himself.
1280 1280
That's the truth.这是事实。
1281 1281
Go back to your brother, boy.
1282 1282
I have got a deadline to meet.
1283 1283
Hello?喂？
1284 1284
Put Ward
on the phone.
1285 1285
Why'd you put his byline
on that article?
1286 1286
How could you sign
his name on that?
1287 1287
Tell him we got
Hillary out.
1288 1288
The governor's
gonna pardon him.
1289 1289
Hillary's getting out.
1290 1290
"I've had some time to think
over the past few months
1291 1291
about me, about you.
1292 1292
I'm not sure I found
what I want out of life yet.
1293 1293
All I know is that I don't want
to live it without you.
1294 1294
Please take this ring back.
Love, Jack. " “
1295 1295
Get the door.
1296 1296
Get the fucking
door, bitch!
1297 1297
Who the fuck are you?你到底是谁？
1298 1298
I'm Hillary.
What you want?你要什么？
1299 1299
Get the fuck out!
I'm with Charlotte.
1300 1300
That bitch took my--
I'll call you later!
1301 1301
Charlotte, you want me
to call the police?
1302 1302
There she is.在那里，她是。
1303 1303
I'm sorry.对不起。
1304 1304
I was gonna write
you a letter--
1305 1305
No, I don't need
your letters. Come here.到这里来。
1306 1306
Uh--呃 -
1307 1307
Don't touch me.不要碰我。
1308 1308
Come on here.
Don't touch you?
1309 1309
1310 1310
It's okay.这没关系。
1311 1311
It's all right, baby.
1312 1312
Anything.任何东西。
1313 1313
That's all right.没关系。
1314 1314
You told me you loved me你告诉我你爱我
in your third letter.
1315 1315
Do you love me?你爱我吗？
1316 1316
Yes!是的！
1317 1317
You always fuck
like this?这样的吗？
1318 1318
Like it was喜欢它
the last time?
1319 1319
Do you think I'm pretty?
1320 1320
You fuck
those niggers like this?
1321 1321
Gonna get all inside here!
1322 1322
Now pack your shit
and let's go.
1323 1323
I don't think I'm gonna like
living in a swamp.
1324 1324
I don't want to live in a swamp.
I like it here.我喜欢这里。
1325 1325
And that was而这
their declaration of love.
1326 1326
So Hillary took
Charlotte to the swamp.
1327 1327
So did you hear
about old man Henry? No.号
1328 1328
He got drunk in his back yard
by the water,
1329 1329
and the alligators came out and took
a big chunk of his leg.
1330 1330
Ha.哈。 Just joking.只是在开玩笑。
1331 1331
My daddy rooster,
he got jumped
1332 1332
by three of his sons,
1333 1333
so I need to find a home
for three of them.
1334 1334
So he's于是，他
in my house sitting,
1335 1335
so I need--I know
you only have hens.
1336 1336
That's why I was wondering,
you know, if you want to babysit,
1337 1337
you know, adopt three
of them for you.
1338 1338
But they'd be good though,
because you have hens. No.号
1339 1339
You're my only hope.
No! “不！” I don't want any.
1340 1340
Come on, Charlotte.
1341 1341
I need you我需要你
to do me a favor.
1342 1342
I need you to post
this thing for me.
1343 1343
It ain't got
a stamp on it.
1344 1344
What's wrong with you today?
It's real important.
1345 1345
You think you can do
that for me?
1346 1346
You're not acting
yourself today.
1347 1347
Why's your door open, huh?
1348 1348
Smells like piss in here.
1349 1349
Ward Ward said
you might show up.
1350 1350
Left him a note.
1351 1351
You stink.
1352 1352
I can smell you
from over here.
1353 1353
Come here, boy.
Come sit down.
1354 1354
What you doing
back in Miami?
1355 1355
Yardley's gone.
1356 1356
He quit?
1357 1357
No.号
1358 1358
He's in New York.
1359 1359
Signing some book deal.
1360 1360
Hero of the new journalism
or some kind of shit. I don't know.我不知道。
1361 1361
W.W. W.W. moved Ellen
into the house, huh?
1362 1362
Whatever.不管。
1363 1363
Whatever makes him happy.
1364 1364
There wasn't
no developer, Jack.
1365 1365
All right, let's move.
1366 1366
Come on,来吧，
go shower, Ward.
1367 1367
I'm tired.我累了。
1368 1368
Come on.来吧。
1369 1369
Jeez.哎呀。
1370 1370
I keep thinking
I missed something, Jack.
1371 1371
Like I missed something
I was supposed to see
1372 1372
that was right
in front of me.在我的面前。
1373 1373
Like what?像什么？
1374 1374
The point of it.
1375 1375
Doesn't matter.无所谓。
1376 1376
Things got out of hand.
1377 1377
You got hurt,
1378 1378
Yardley got
his fucking book deal.
1379 1379
Hillary got Charlotte
in the swamp.
1380 1380
The idea--is that--
you run the water
1381 1381
while you're
in there with it.
1382 1382
Come on, man.来吧，伙计。
1383 1383
Hey.嘿。
1384 1384
What if we didn't get
it right, huh?
1385 1385
Makes no difference.没有什么区别。
1386 1386
It makes no difference,
Jack?杰克？
1387 1387
You don't know你不知道
what it feels like
1388 1388
to get it
exactly right now.
1389 1389
To get it down just
the way it happened.
1390 1390
You're going你会
back to see Hillary.
1391 1391
Fuck yeah, I am.
1392 1392
Do you ever hear
from her?
1393 1393
No.号
1394 1394
Miss Bless?
No.号
1395 1395
I wonder what she thinks
of him now, huh?
1396 1396
Can't see her sitting
on the porch stoop
1397 1397
holding a silver spoon
1398 1398
and waiting for the ice cream carton
to come her way, can you?
1399 1399
I dug around.
1400 1400
There wasn't no proof,
no how, nowhere
1401 1401
that they was ever
stealing sod that night.
1402 1402
They want me
to keep my mouth shut.
1403 1403
Don't want me to tell my story.
Well, fuck them.
1404 1404
I'm gonna tell my story.
I'm gonna write my story,
1405 1405
and they can publish it
wherever the fuck they want to.
1406 1406
Yeah, Mama always said
you better be--
1407 1407
right and be last before you gonna be
first and be wrong, boy.
1408 1408
Be right and be last before you go
gonna be first and be wrong--
1409 1409
Yeah, I know!是啊，我知道！
1410 1410
I heard--
They said things about--
1411 1411
Oh, yeah.哦，是的。
It's all true.这一切都是真的。
1412 1412
Just kidding.只是在开玩笑。
You should see the other guy.
1413 1413
Smile.微笑。
1414 1414
Thank you.谢谢。
1415 1415
Everyone, please.
We're cutting the cake!
1416 1416
Where's the photographer?
1417 1417
Hey, Claire,
can you hand me
1418 1418
that salt over there?
1419 1419
Thank you.谢谢。
1420 1420
Hi.你好。
1421 1421
You ain't supposed
to be in here.
1422 1422
You gonna get me in--
I got you a drink.
1423 1423
You know你知道吗
W. W. fired me.
1424 1424
I'm gonna talk
to your boss
1425 1425
and tell him you're a friend
of the family.
1426 1426
No, Jack.
Yeah.是啊。
1427 1427
All I ever did was cook
and clean for you boys.
1428 1428
I wasn't never no family.
1429 1429
Anyway, go on back outside.
1430 1430
Well, Ward's out there.
You gonna come see him?
1431 1431
Are you trying
to get me fired?
1432 1432
I miss you.我很想念你。
1433 1433
I got something for you.我有东西给你。
Wait a minute.等待一分钟。
1434 1434
This came for you
about a month ago.
1435 1435
She told him to tell-
1436 1436
She told him她告诉他，
not to let you see it.
1437 1437
"Dear Jack,
I can't believe我简直不敢相信
1438 1438
I'm finally writing you
this letter
1439 1439
or if it will get to you
1440 1440
or whether
you'll even read it.
1441 1441
Jack, I think I've really
messed up this time.
1442 1442
Don't misunderstand me.
1443 1443
Hillary lo ves me,
in his way.
1444 1444
It's just me that isn't made
for this place,
1445 1445
for this lifestyle.
1446 1446
I hope I can make it
to your father's wedding
1447 1447
so I can hear you tell me,
'I told you so.'
1448 1448
Take care for now.
Sweetly, your Charlotte. " “
1449 1449
Is that from blondie?
1450 1450
Thank you.谢谢。
1451 1451
Where's your hat?
1452 1452
Oh, I forgot.哦，我忘了。
Get out of the kitchen.
1453 1453
I'm sorry.对不起。
1454 1454
Excuse me.对不起。 I'm Jack Jansen.
I'm the groom's son.
1455 1455
My father wants to know
what exactly is taking dinner so long.
1456 1456
It'll be ready in a minute, sir.
Thank you.谢谢。
1457 1457
Put the hair
under the hat.
1458 1458
I don't want your black hair
in my food.
1459 1459
You can put your black hair
in my food.
1460 1460
Cheers.的欢呼声。
1461 1461
Bye, Anita.
1462 1462
Bye, Jack.
1463 1463
You wouldn't leave
without me, would you?
1464 1464
Drop you off at the motel.
I'm going somewhere.
1465 1465
Mind me asking where
you're going afterwards?
1466 1466
Going to Charlotte's.
1467 1467
Well, it gotta be tonight?
1468 1468
I got to get her
the fuck out of there.
1469 1469
I got to get her
out of there!
1470 1470
Charlotte's acting
on her own free will.
1471 1471
What do you want me
to say?说什么？ Move.移动。
1472 1472
I got to go
to the Van Wetters' anyway.
1473 1473
Come with me跟我来
tomorrow morning.
1474 1474
We're going now.
It ain't the right time.
1475 1475
Get the fuck out my way.
You ain't driving drunk like this.
1476 1476
What the fuck are you gonna
do about it, huh?
1477 1477
What?什么？
1478 1478
Charlotte must be
a good piece of ass.
1479 1479
You look like a pirate.
I know.我知道。
1480 1480
Do this for me
one time. Go "Aargh. "
1481 1481
Uh-huh.嗯。
1482 1482
Hey, you're driving
all squirrelly, man.
1483 1483
Hey, Jack,
sit on down. Hey.嘿。
1484 1484
You sure
it's this way?
1485 1485
I'm sure我敢肯定，
it's this way.
1486 1486
Ain't a good time to be drinking
too much out here, Jack.
1487 1487
Yeah, you're one to talk.
1488 1488
Keeping your promise
to Dad, did you?
1489 1489
Not to drink
on his big day?
1490 1490
How you holding up?
1491 1491
Let's see your hands.
Are they shaking?
1492 1492
They shaking, Ward, huh?
Don't drink.
1493 1493
Well, why do you take
after the worst of me, Jack?
1494 1494
'Cause you're my brother.
1495 1495
Wedding party, Charlotte?
1496 1496
I'm going我要去
to the wedding.
1497 1497
Don't be difficult.
I told you--
1498 1498
I don't want you to go.我不想让你走。
1499 1499
No. I told you. I'm going to我要
the wedding.
1500 1500
Watch out.看出来。
1501 1501
God, it smells
like shit.像屎一样。
1502 1502
Electric fence.
You all right?你没事吧？
1503 1503
1504 1504
Goddamn.该死的。
1505 1505
You let me lead.
1506 1506
I don't want to quarrel
with you.和你在一起。
1507 1507
You're my little pony.
1508 1508
I just want to climb
up on you one more time.
1509 1509
I can't believe我简直不敢相信
she'd live here.
1510 1510
Charlotte!夏洛特！
1511 1511
Charlotte?夏洛特？
1512 1512
Charlotte!夏洛特！
1513 1513
What you want?你要什么？
1514 1514
She not here.
1515 1515
She gone.
1516 1516
What is it you want
with my wife?
1517 1517
Huh?咦？
1518 1518
What is it you want
with my wife?
1519 1519
Just wanted
to say hello.
1520 1520
A quick hello and a quick poke
while you're at it?
1521 1521
How about you?你怎么样？
What you up to, Ward?
1522 1522
I know what you came for.
1523 1523
I got what you want.我得到了你想要的。
1524 1524
Where is she?她在哪里？
1525 1525
How should I know?我怎么知道？
I'm not leaving until I see her.
1526 1526
She not here.
She gone.
1527 1527
Let's go.让我们去。
Where?在哪里？
1528 1528
How should I know?我怎么知道？
1529 1529
Last night昨晚
she told me她告诉我，
1530 1530
she was going
to your father's wedding!
1531 1531
You're a liar!
We just come from there!
1532 1532
And that's where you
should go back to, boy!
1533 1533
He's lying!
1534 1534
He's lying.
1535 1535
I got this.我得到了这一点。
Go back to the boat.
1536 1536
Where is she?她在哪里？
1537 1537
Stop provoking me, boy,
1538 1538
and do what your brother
tells you!
1539 1539
I said I'm not leaving
until I see her!
1540 1540
Goddamn it,
he killed her.
1541 1541
He killed her, Ward.
1542 1542
You killed her!
1543 1543
You son of a bitch!你狗娘养的！
1544 1544
That's all you were good
for is killing her!
1545 1545
Huh?咦？
1546 1546
Run, Jack!
1547 1547
Come on, boy.来吧，孩子。
Show me.让我看看。
1548 1548
I'm gonna fuck you up.
1549 1549
Come on!来吧！
1550 1550
Jack!杰克！
1551 1551
Ward!
1552 1552
1553 1553
Is this这是
what you wanted?
1554 1554
Yeah.是啊。
1555 1555
You got
what you come for.
1556 1556
Paperboy.
1557 1557
Where you going,
paperboy?
1558 1558
Ain't no way
out of this one.
1559 1559
Fuck you!你他妈的！
1560 1560
Hillary Van Wetter希拉里·范·多雨
was tried and convicted
1561 1561
in the murders of Charlotte Bless
and Ward Jansen.
1562 1562
He died in the electric chair
at the Florida State Prison.
1563 1563
Nobody ever found
out who murdered Sheriff Call.
1564 1564
My little Jack finally saw his mama
again at Ward's funeral.
1565 1565
He became a writer
of some renown.
1566 1566
He never did get
over his first true love.
_addload(function());